M. RAYHAN FUADI

Cirebon, 45135 | +6281312320755 | fuadi.work@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/rayhanfuadi

Summary

Extroverted and energetic 3rd year Industrial Engineering student from Institut Teknologi Bandung that has a passion for product management with strong interpersonal and leadership skills with a bunch of organization experiences and strong basic knowledge in data analytics with Python, data engineering (SQL, R Programming), front-end development (HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Front-End Libraries), UI/UX design (AdobeXD) and public speaking,

Education

Institut Teknologi Bandung

Industrial Engineering, Bachelor's Degree

• Courses taken: 75

SMA Negeri 2 Cirebon 2017 — 2019

Science

- 3rd Winner of Informatics City Olimpiad (OSK Komputer) Cirebon 2018
- 3rd Best Graduate Awardee of SMA Negeri 2 Cirebon 2019
- Student of acceleration program (Graduated in 2 years).

Experience

Cirebon in Charity (CIC) – Nonprofit Education Organization in Cirebon

Head of Academic: Motivation Division — Ring 1 CIC X 2020/2021

Jul 2020 — Aug 2021

2019 — 2023 (Expected)

GPA: 3.33/4.00

- Designing 1-year motivation curriculum and initiating 1st edition of motivation module
- Liaising and maintaining good relationship with external and internal motivators
- Giving speeches at motivation session of CIC students

Math and Science SBMPTN Module Staff— Academic Division CIC IX

Aug 2019 – Jun 2020

- Provide answers and explanation of Mathematics and Physics test problems
- Collaborating with many students across universities to make UTBK modules

Udrussunnah Bandung – Islamic Student Organization based in Bandung

Head of Islamic Event Organizer — Lembaga Kajian dan Daurah Udrussunnah

Oct 2020 — Mar 2021

- Overall in-charge of the event and reporting monthly update to the donators.
- Designing and executing project management of Islamic lectures (Kajian dan Tabligh Akbar Islami)
- Liaising and maintaining good relationship with the audiences and lecturers

Graphic Designer and Content Strategist – Instagram @udrussunnah

Dec 2020 — Apr 2021

- Designing overall grand theme and concept of feed
- Designing 1-3 posters per week, including microblog/carousel posts
- Achieving more than 100-300% engagement, reach, and added followers in less than a year

Honor & Awards

MTI Data Analytics Club Mini Competition— Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Industri ITB

Top 10 teams of Data Analysis using Python Competition

September 2019

Hackathon Cloud Computing AWS Amazon — IEEE ITB x Taiwan Tech and eCloudvalley

Top 10 teams of Hackathon IoT and Cloud Computing using AWS Amazon

National Physics Tournament — Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia First Runner-Up of National Physics Tournament, Physics Festival 4.0 October 2019

Projects & Certification

Certificate of Responsive Web Design – Freecodecamp.org

July 2020 — (no expiration date)

Certification of learning the languages that developers use to build webpages: HTML (Hypertext Markup Language) for content, and CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) for design. Check out the certificate here.

Personal Portfolio Webpage Project – Final test of Responsive Web Design

July 2020

Building complete portfolio webpage of my personal branding from the scratch only by using HTML and CSS. I designed the UI/UX in Adobe XD and complete the project within 1 week. Check out my work here.

"Arbain untuk Anak", A Static-Responsive Documentation Webpage

July 2020

Making a static-responsive documentation webpage of *Arbain*, a little book of hadeeth of Prophet Muhammad PBUH's word, from scratches only by using HTML and CSS in 3 days. This page is designed to make easier for kids to memorize and understand basic Islamic knowledge. Check out the website here.

"Senyum Kita" Project of Static-Responsive Landing Page

June 2020

Building a static-responsive landing page for Senyum Kita social project of Udrussunnah. Providing 3 donating plan to the donators to make donating easier. Check out the webpage here.

Muhandis Program Registration Form Webpage

June 2020

Mahad Muhandis is one of Islamic educational institution in Bandung. I built the entire interface website prototype using only HTML and CSS from the scratches in 2 days. Check out the webpage here.

Optimizing Vaccine Distribution in Indonesia using Mixed Integer Programming Algorithm April 2021 Operational Research I Course Final Project

Operational Research I course final project of implementing mixed integer-binary programming algorithm to optimize vaccine distribution in four big cities in Jawa: Jakarta, Bandung, Surabaya, and Semarang.

Arduino-Based Design of Hand Sanitizer Dispenser – Final Project of Industrial Eletronics May 2021 Designing Arduino-based automated hand sanitizer dispenser in response to the needs of minimizing contact and COVID-19 virus spread using TinkerCAD.

Skills & Abilities

Indonesian (Native), English, Arabic, Microsoft Office, SOLIDWORKS, Programming Skills (Javascript, Python, C++, MATLAB), Data Engineering (Microsoft SQL and R Programming), Data Analytics with Python, Front-End Development (HTML, CSS, JS, and other front-end libraries: Bootstrap, JQuery, SASS, React), Teaching Skills, Writing Skill (Report & Paper), Public Speaking and Presentation Skills.